Theo Haines

Web developer and Retail assistant

Yeovil

theohaines@yahoo.com

+44 7478 634076

I'm a student at Yeovil College studying a T-Level in software development and design, I am passionate in computing and web development. I have two years experience in sales and customer support from Currys and Carphone Warehouse. Some of my skills include Software development, Mobile contract / insurance sales, Customer service, Web development and games development.

Personal Details

Driver's License: None

Industry: IT Operations & Helpdesk, Retail, Sales, Software Development, Technology

Total years of experience: 2

Work Experience

Mobile sales

Carphone Warehouse, UK - Yeovil December 2022 to Present

I have experience working in mobile contract and insurance sales as well as stock operations inside Carphone warehouse and customer service. I have experience setting up mobile phones and diagnosing faults on mobile phones too.

Customer Support

Currys Team Know How - Yeovil September 2021 to Present

I help people with many problems they could have this tech they have purchased form one of our stores and online department as well as come up with solutions to help the customer in the best way possible.

CNC Programmer

Self Employment - South Petherton January 2021 to Present

I work on a CNC machine periodically and have experience in running the mill and using the software solid works to create toolpaths.

Education

A-Level in Computer Science

Yeovil College - Yeovil September 2021 to Present

GCSE in Photography

Stanchester Academy - Stoke-Sub-Hamdon May 2019 to June 2021

GCSE in Computer Science

Stanchester Academy - Stoke-Sub-Hamdon July 2016 to June 2021

GCSE in English

Stanchester Academy - Stoke-Sub-Hamdon July 2016 to June 2021

GCSE in Mathematics

Stanchester Academy - Stoke-Sub-Hamdon July 2016 to June 2021

Skills

- Customer Support (2 years)
- Customer Service (2 years)
- Communication skills
- Computer skills (7 years)
- Web design (2 years)
- Sales (2 years)
- Mobile sales (1 year)

Links

https://Theohaines.xyz

Certifications and Licenses

Google device certification 2022

October 2022 to Present

Recognised for being a Google device expert—someone customers and colleagues can turn to for answers, help, and advice on all things Google.

Google device certification 2023

December 2022 to October 2023

This certificate confirms successful completion of the Devices Certification by Google, showing exemplary knowledge and understanding of the products and services within the Google ecosystem. This certificate is valid to October 1, 2023.